KARTHIKA KOLLURU () Featured

Application Specialist seeking assignment in Software Development, Software Application Development, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Application Maintenance, Software Design, IT infrastructure

Management, .NET, SQL, VBA, Javascript, HTML



Current Designation: Application Specialist Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 4 Month(s)

Current Company: Parexel International Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Vijayawada Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computer Science Eng.]

Pref. Location: Chennai

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Application Specialist, Software Developer, Software Development, Software Application Development, Project

Management, Requirement Gathering, Application Maintenance, Software Design, IT infrastructure

Management, NET, Angular JS, SQL, VBA, Javascript, HTML, CSS

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

Application with 4+ years of experience organizing presentations, preparing facility reports, and maintaining the utmost confidentiality. Possess a B.E. in Computer Science. Looking to leverage my knowledge and experience into a role as Application Developer.

Work Experience

Parexel International as Application Specialist

Feb 2015 to Till Date

Parexel International as Application Specialist

Feb 2015 to Jun 2019

PAREXEL International as APPLICATION SPECIALIST

Feb 2015 to Jun 2019

Have experience and expertise in installation of various software and operating systems namely Windows 2010/3/XP/7

Have Expertise in using search engine tools and Internet.

Providing first-level technical support for IT infrastructure.

Expertise in the usage of MS office tools namely word, MS- Excel, Power point, MS-Access.

Responsible for tasks to the end users through remotely/ Email/ Call.

Ability to install and verify software package installations.

Application Maintenance/ Bug fixing (INTRANET).

Knowledge of standard software systems.

Strong in Communication and Involved in regular review meetings.

Developed few VBA applications in my internal organization.

PROJECTS

Have experience and expertise in installation of various software and operating systems namely Windows 2010/3/XP/7 /Vista.

Have Expertise in using search engine tools and Internet.

Providing first-level technical support for IT infrastructure.

Expertise in the usage of MS office tools namely word, MS- Excel, Power point, MS-Access.

Responsible for tasks to the end users through remotely/ Email/ Call.

Ability to install and verify software package installations.

Application Maintenance/ Bug fixing (INTRANET).

Knowledge of standard software systems.

Strong in Communication and Involved in regular review meetings.

Developed few VBA applications in my internal organization.

The following are the projects done in PAREXEL organization. PAREXEL International Pvt.Ltd. is a diversified global Clinical Research Organization that gives technological solutions to business enterprises around the world.

PAREXEL Access Strategy tool (Front-end and Back-end Developer)

E-budget (Front-end and Back-end Developer)

Rates Data Base (Front-end and Back-end Developer)

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science Eng.) from PYDAH ENG and TECH. JNTUK, Vizag. in 2014

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
.NET(VB & ASP)	
Angular js	
SQL	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
telugu	Expert			

Affirmative Action

Category: OBC - non-creamy

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time